Hello, now I will tell you about filling the Tata
AIG General Insurance Co. motor claim
form and how to do the motor claim
intimation.
So first of all, go to Google and
search for Tata ABG Motor Claim Form PDF and after searching, a video will
appear which will be in blue color, you have to
download it, it is visible near and far from,
you download it, this is the
latest from, in this you will see a toll free
number, after calling on this toll free number,
keep your driving license and insurance copy and RC book with you, after that you will call on the toll free number,
then the solution will be
posted, after that you will explain your stand clearly on this,
after that as soon as any
assistant calls, then after that you have to tell how your
car met with an
accident, how were you
going from where, let me tell you about that
booklet, friend, you will keep giving information to the curious, as soon as
you get the claim intimation,
after being in the market, you will be
given a clean form, a claim number will be given,
you have to fill that clean number here, the
clean number is visible  But in that you have to
give him the policy number,
then give your vehicle number, vehicle number whichever
is yours, T-20 ABCD, okay, after that in
COD or
this placement name plate, in which inch and
name means the name in whose name the vehicle
is, you have to give the full name here,
after that you enter the email ID here,
enter this address, whatever address is
inside, look at it, enter the
mobile number here, enter this PIN number
and after that the
description of the accident
description means information about the accident, if
your vehicle met with an accident then there is information
about it and if your
vehicle was stolen then there is information about it, so
look at the time and date of
accidents, that is, it happened at this time, you have to
enter it here, at what time it happened, it happened
or you will tick on 9th and if it is PM then you have to
click on PM, after that take the
day on which the vehicle met with an accident, you will enter the
20th, 12th month 2014 2012 2020,
subscribe at this place, there is a massage
in Raipur, Chhattisgarh  Or here you will write
subscribe, subscribe means we will do it
in a hurry and if any
opponent has
died due to any leg fracture then
you will have to tick the third party verification
on any of our body inches here
and if there is any third party verification then we will
present the properties, after that when we
go down then it is writing
short description of accident, that is,
in short you have to tell how your car met with an
accident, from where to where were you going,
how did your car meet with an
accident, suppose while
saving an animal your vehicle got unbalanced, met with an
accident and overturned, then you have to
fill it completely here, after that see
driver details and time of accident, that is,
who was driving that vehicle at the time of accident,
fill in the name of the driver and
enter what he does, enter the
driving license number, if they
get the number then they just enter it, if there is no number here then we will do it,
now can he
drive a scooter or soon then it means it is being scrubbed
and subscribe,
now first of all like there is a truck, it is a cargo carrier  If the
Bolero Maxi truck pickup is cut, then
here you have to enter the permitted date, which
permit is it, whether it is a permit or a national permit, then
enter the fitness, till when is the fitness of the vehicle, load
carrier time option means what type
of goods was being transported, okay, number of
cases, how many people were sitting in the vehicle, that has to be
entered on the Sangh and if any kind of
loss has been caused to the party or someone has to be
subscribed, then the police station case number
and record have been entered
and after that if any third party or any
new property has been damaged, then
you have to fill in its complete information here, name,
address, whatever it is, you have to enter it,
after that the important instruction is that
accident occurred by using diagram, that is,
score's accident, how does it mean
for Meghwal, okay and after subscribing here,
for payment, you have to make the payment in the account, that
means hatred in the school,
here is the PAN number, then subscribe to the channel,
enter the bank address of Jaipur main branch address here, then it
is necessary to enter its city, PIN number, Muktibodh IFSC code, after that if the type of account is
different from your account then it will be removed
and if  If we do it, we will do it, then we will fix it,
then the account number is online at the bottom, so I will go there
easily, then I will see the email ID,
enter the account number where after that enter the
email ID, all this should be done on your computer, then
with this, whoever will do the survey, give
this form to the surveyor completely,
after filling it completely, write the name of that place
here and put it here and sign, along with this
you have to give the
copy of RC to the server, you have to give the copy of Jansi, you have to
give the copy of insurance and the driving
license should be absolutely clear,
I am a dealer of Aarti engine license, so
you have to give fitness permit and tax also,
one thing which is enough is that you have to give all that,
after that give the form to the surveyor after completing all this,
okay, okay, tell me to watch the video,
thank you, if you liked this video then
like and share it, subscribe to our channel,
thank you.